Contact

sdcortright@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/shayhna-lowry-5744a2128 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Healthcare

Hospitals

Healthcare Management

Certifications

CMSRN

Honors-Awards

Daisy Award Nominee
Sigma Theta Tau
Jonathan McBride Block Recipient

Shayhna Lowry

RN II at Medical University of South Carolina

Charleston, South Carolina

Summary

Experienced healthcare professional and strong patient advocate with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Nursing Education, Surgical Oncology, Oncology Nursing, Patient Safety, and Acute Care. Master's degree prepared, focused in Nursing Education from Walden University; certified in Medical-Surgical Nursing and approved as a chemo and bio therapy provider.

Experience

Medical University of South Carolina RN II April 2019 - Present (1 year 4 months) Charleston, South Carolina Area

FlexCare Medical Staffing RN April 2018 - Present (2 years 4 months)

HealthSouth Rehabiltation RN Supervisor November 2017 - April 2018 (6 months) North Charleston, SC

Medical University of South Carolina RN 2010 - March 2018 (8 years)

Education

Walden University
Master's degree, Nursing Education

Trident Technical College

Associate's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse